yes hello um hello
everyone yes welcome to
uh to my
stream welcome welcome welcome to my
stream Welcome to My
Stream well I want to talk about
uh insurance ins
policies I'm talk about insurance
policies
uh but life
insurance basically endowment
policies uh the most common policy that
we sell is uh
Prive
credential insurance so if a child is in
primary
school or for example if a child is in a
yeah Primary
School uh you can save up um until the
child you can serve up for second school
if the child is in secondary school you
can serve up um then the child uh gets
money for
University then uh there is the pr
Dollar
Save um you can save $100 per month
month and uh and
yeah and there's a PO investor
Place uh this one it's a life endowment
policy you save up to 60 years 55 years
65 years 70
years yeah thank you for listening